Context-free grammars are a big step towards being able to say what we want in
上下文无关文法是朝着能够表达我们想要的内容迈出的一大步
a parser but, we still need some other things. First of all, a context-free
一个解析器，但是，我们还需要一些其他的东西。首先，一个上下文无关的
grammar at least as we define it so far, just gives us a yes or no answer. Yes
至少按照我们到目前为止的定义，语法只能给我们一个是或否的答案。是
something, yes a string is in the language of the Context-free grammar or no it is
某样东西，是字符串是上下文无关文法的语言，还是不是
not. We also need a method for building a Parse Tree at the input. So in those cases
不。我们还需要一种在输入端构建解析树的方法。所以在这些情况下
where it is on the language, we need to know how it's in the language. We need the
它在语言中的位置，我们需要知道它是如何在语言中出现的。我们需要的是
actual Parse Tree not just yes or no. In the cases where the string is not in the
实际的解析树不只是是或不是。在字符串不在
language, we have to be able to handle errors gracefully and give some kind of
语言，我们必须能够优雅地处理错误，并给出某种
feedback to the programmer so we need a method for doing that. And finally if we
反馈给程序员，所以我们需要一种方法来做到这一点。最后如果我们
have these two things we need an actual implementation of them in order to
有了这两件事，我们需要它们的实际实现，以便
actually implement context-free grammars. One last comment before we wrap up this
实际上实现了上下文无关文法。在我们结束这件事之前还有最后一条评论
video. The form of the context-free grammar can be important. Tools are often
录像带。上下文无关文法的形式可能很重要。工具通常是
sensitive to the particular you write the grammar and while there are many ways to
对你所写的语法的具体细节很敏感，虽然有很多方法可以
write a grammar for the same language, only some of them may be accepted by the
编写同一种语言的语法，则只有部分语法可能会被
tools. And as we'll see there are cases where it's necessary to modify the grammar
工具。正如我们将看到的，在某些情况下需要修改语法
in order to get the tools to accept it. This happens actually sometimes as well
为了让工具接受它。这实际上有时也会发生。
with regular expressions but it's much less common. So normally for most regular
使用正则表达式，但它不太常见。所以通常情况下，对于大多数普通的人来说
expressions you would want to write the tools would be able to digest them. That's
您想要编写的工具表达式将能够消化它们。那是
fine. That's not also true. That's not true of an arbitrary context-free grammar.
很好。这也不是真的。这不适用于任意的上下文无关文法。